<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Arkham Horror LCG Campaign Guide</string>

    <string-array name="expansion_names">
        <item>The Dunwich Legacy</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Investigator name strings-->
    <string-array name="investigators">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Roland Banks</item>
        <item>Daisy Walker</item>
        <item>Skids O\'Toole</item>
        <item>Agnes Baker</item>
        <item>Wendy Adams</item>
        <item>Zoey Samaras</item>
        <item>Rex Murphy</item>
        <item>Jenny Barnes</item>
        <item>Jim Culver</item>
        <item>\"Ashcan\" Pete</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="choose_investigators">Choose Investigators</string>
    <string name="roland_banks">Roland Banks</string>
    <string name="daisy_walker">Daisy Walker</string>
    <string name="skids_otoole">Skids O\'Toole</string>
    <string name="agnes_baker">Agnes Baker</string>
    <string name="wendy_adams">Wendy Adams</string>
    <string name="zoey_samaras">Zoey Samaras</string>
    <string name="rex_murphy">Rex Murphy</string>
    <string name="jenny_barnes">Jenny Barnes</string>
    <string name="jim_culver">Jim Culver</string>
    <string name="ashcan_pete">\"Ashcan\" Pete</string>
    <string name="cover_up">Unresolved Cover Up in play</string>
    <string name="hospital_debts">Unresolved Hospital Debts in play</string>
    <string name="smite_the_wicked">Unresolved Smite the Wicked in play</string>
    <string name="searching_for_izzie">Unresolved Searching for Izzie in play</string>

    <!--Strings for player cards-->
    <string-array name="player_cards">
        <item>Strange Solution identified</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="strange_solution">You have identified the solution.\n</string>

    <!--Strings for the investigator defeated spinner-->
    <string-array name="investigator_eliminated">
        <item>Not eliminated</item>
        <item>Resigned</item>
        <item>Defeated by damage</item>
        <item>Defeated by horror</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Strings for the resolution spinner-->
    <string-array name="resolutions_two">
        <item>No resolution</item>
        <item>Resolution 1</item>
        <item>Resolution 2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="resolutions_three">
        <item>No resolution</item>
        <item>Resolution 1</item>
        <item>Resolution 2</item>
        <item>Resolution 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="resolutions_four">
        <item>No resolution</item>
        <item>Resolution 1</item>
        <item>Resolution 2</item>
        <item>Resolution 3</item>
        <item>Resolution 4</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Difficulty strings-->
    <string-array name="difficulty">
        <item>Easy</item>
        <item>Standard</item>
        <item>Hard</item>
        <item>Expert</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="difficulty_two">
        <item>Standard</item>
        <item>Hard</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="one">1</string>
    <string name="two">2</string>
    <string name="three">3</string>
    <string name="chaos_bag">Chaos Bag</string>
    <string name="plus_two">+2</string>
    <string name="plus_one">+1</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="minus_one">-1</string>
    <string name="minus_two">-2</string>
    <string name="minus_three">-3</string>
    <string name="minus_four">-4</string>
    <string name="minus_five">-5</string>
    <string name="minus_six">-6</string>
    <string name="minus_seven">-7</string>
    <string name="minus_eight">-8</string>
    <string name="skull">Skull</string>
    <string name="cultist">Cultist</string>
    <string name="tablet">Tablet</string>
    <string name="elder_thing">Elder Thing</string>
    <string name="tentacles">Tentacles</string>
    <string name="elder_sign">Elder Sign</string>

    <!--Miscellaneous other UI strings-->
    <string name="saved_campaigns">Saved Campaigns</string>
    <string name="current_campaign">Current campaign: </string>
    <string name="current_scenario">Current scenario: </string>
    <string name="physical_trauma">Physical trauma: </string>
    <string name="mental_trauma">Mental trauma: </string>
    <string name="available_xp">Available XP: </string>
    <string name="spent_xp">XP Spent: </string>
    <string name="eliminated">Eliminated: </string>
    <string name="negative">-</string>
    <string name="positive">+</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="lead_investigator">Lead investigator: </string>
    <string name="victory_display">Victory display: </string>
    <string name="campaign_name">Campaign name</string>
    <string name="player_name">Player name</string>
    <string name="decklist">Decklist URL</string>
    <string name="setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="sets">Encounter sets: </string>
    <string name="locations">Starting locations: </string>
    <string name="set_aside">Set aside: </string>
    <string name="additional">Additional setup: </string>
    <string name="campaign_log">Campaign Log</string>
    <string name="nothing">Nothing to show.</string>
    <string name="lost">The investigators have lost.</string>
    <string name="expacs_owned">Expansions owned</string>
    <string name="pick_expacs_owned">Pick expansions owned</string>
    <string name="standalone">Standalone scenario</string>
    <string name="add_side_story">Add side story</string>
    <string name="player_cards">Player cards</string>
    <string name="pick_option">Pick an option</string>
    <string name="scenario_not_available">This scenario is not available yet.</string>
    <string name="campaign_completed">Campaign completed</string>
    <string-array name="campaign_options">
        <item>Finish and delete campaign</item>
        <item>Night of the Zealot</item>
        <item>The Dunwich Legacy</item>
    </string-array>


    <!--Night of the Zealot-->

    <string name="night_campaign_name">Night of the Zealot</string>
    <string name="night_scenario_one">Scenario 1: The Gathering</string>
    <string name="night_scenario_two">Scenario 2: The Midnight Masks</string>
    <string name="night_scenario_three">Scenario 3: The Devourer Below</string>

    <string name="night_setup">Friday, September 18, 1925. Arkham, Massachusetts. It is the end of
    a long and abnormally hot summer. The first hints of autumn beckon, but a heavy heat persists,
    relentless. A silent, unspoken anger grips the town. Tempers are short, and in the last week
    alone there have been numerous reports of townspeople coming to heated, violent blows with one
    another over simple misunderstandings.\n
        \nAnd now, a call from James Hankerson, he claims to have found a dismembered body in his barn.\n
        \nBlaming the weather would be too easy. There is something wrong with this town, and not a
        whole lot this old soothsayer can do to stop the slide. My auguries indicate a small group
        of investigators will soon take note of these strange happenings and set forth to make
        things right. I\'ll be watching their progress&#8230;but I won\'t be holding my breath.</string>

    <!--Miscellaneous-->
    <string name="ghoul_priest_additional">Shuffle the Ghoul Priest into the encounter deck.\n</string>
    <string name="ghoul_priest_checkbox">Ghoul Priest killed</string>
    <string name="cultists_interrogated">Cultists interrogated: \n</string>
    <string name="cultists_got_away">Cultists got away: \n</string>
    <string name="drew">"Wolf-Man" Drew</string>
    <string name="herman">Herman Collins</string>
    <string name="peter">Peter Warren</string>
    <string name="victoria">Victoria Devereux</string>
    <string name="ruth">Ruth Turner</string>
    <string name="masked_hunter">The Masked Hunter</string>
    <string name="no_changes">No changes are made.\n</string>

    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="house_standing">Your house is still standing.\n</string>
    <string name="house_burned">Your house has burned to the ground.\n</string>
    <string name="ghoul_priest_alive">The Ghoul Priest is still alive.\n</string>
    <string name="lita_forced">Lita was forced to find others to help her cause.\n</string>
    <string name="past_midnight">It is past midnight.\n</string>

    <!--Scenario One - The Gathering-->

    <string name="gathering_setup"><b>Scenario 1: The Gathering</b>\n
        \nYou and your partners have been investigating strange events
        taking place in your home city of Arkham, Massachusetts. Over the past few weeks, several
        townspeople have mysetriously gone missing. Recently, their corpses turned up in the woods,
        savaged and half-eaten. The police and newspapers have stated that wild animals are
        responsible, but you believe there is something else going on. You are gathered together at
        the lead investigator\'s home to discuss these bizarre events.</string>

    <string name="gathering_sets">The Gathering, Rats, Ghouls, Striking Fear, Ancient Evils, and Chilling Cold.</string>
    <string name="gathering_locations">Put the Study location into play.\n</string>
    <string name="gathering_set_aside">All other locations, the Ghoul Priest and Lita Chantler.\n</string>

    <string name="gathering_no_resolution">You barely managed to escape your house with your lives.
    The woman from your parlor follows you out the front door, slamming it behind her. \"You fools!
    See what you have done?\" She pushes a chair in front of the door, lodging it beneath the
    doorknob. \"We must get out of here. Come with me, and I will tell you what I know. We are the
    only ones who can stop the threat that lurks beneath from being unleashed throughout the city.\"
    You\'re in no state to argue. Nodding, you follow the woman as she runs from your front porch out
    into the rainy street, toward Rivertown.\n
    \n<b>The lead investigator earns the Lita Chantler card.</b></string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_one">You nod and allow the red-haired woman to set the walls
    and floor of your house ablaze. The fire spreads quickly, and you run out the front door to
    avoid being caught in the inferno. From the sidewalk, you watch as everything you own is
    consumed by the flames. \"Come with me,\" the woman says. \"You must be told of the threat that
    lurks below. Alone, we are surely doomed&#8230;but together, we can stop it.\"\n
    \n<b>The lead investigator earns the Lita Chantler card.</b></string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_two">You refuse to follow the overzealous woman\'s order and
    kick her out of your home for fear that she will set it ablaze without your permission. \"Fools!
    You are making a grave mistake!\" she warns. \"You do not understand the threat that lurks below
    &#8230;the grave danger we are all in!\" Still shaken by the night\'s events, you decide to hear
    the woman out. Perhaps she can shed some light on these bizarre events&#8230;but she doesn\'t
    seem to trust you very much.</string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_three">You run to the hallway to try to find a way to escape
    the house, but the burning-hot barrier still blocks your parth. Trapped, the horde of feral
    creatures that have invaded your home close in, and you have nowhere to run.\n
    \n<b>All investigators who haven\'t resigned are killed.</b>\n
    \n<b>If the lead investigator is killed, choose an investigator to earn the Lita Chandler card.</b></string>

    <!--Scenario Two - The Midnight Masks-->

    <string name="midnight_setup_a"><b>Scenario 2: The Midnight Masks</b>\n
        \nThe woman came to you in a panic, raving about monsters emerging from the ground in a home near Rivertown.
        \"I managed to trap them,\" she explains, \"but there are others. Other pits. Other domains.\" Only last
        week, you would have thought she was a lunatic. Recent events, however, have challenged your preconceptions
        of normality. You decide to hear her out.\n
    \nShe introduces herself as Lita Chantler and lays out a tale that strains the limits of your
    belief. \"The creatures I speak of,\" she claims, \"are called ghouls - cruel beings who plague
    the crypts, caverns, and tunnels beneath the city of Arkham&#8230;\"\n
    \n\"These creatures feed on the corpses of humans, and they are
    served by a dark cult within Arkham whose members have inexplicably come to worship the ancient
    master of the ghouls. This cult has been killing innocent people and feeding them to the ghouls,
    satiating a monstrous hunger. A dark balance was maintained. Until now. Recently,\" Lita continues,
    \"one of their lairs, where the corpses were stored, was destroyed. Since then, the ghouls have
    been more active than usual. I have tracked their movements and tried my best to stop them from
    running amok throughout the city. But I think there is something worse going on. The cult has been
    planning something darker, and more ominous, than anything I have yet observed. Indicates are
    that this plan shall come to fruition tonight, shortly after midnight. Beyond that, I cannot
    fathom what to expect.\n
    \n\"Many of the cultists,\" Lita continues, \"will seem like everyday people, despite their foul
    intentions. Whenever the cult meets, its members don masks shaped like the skulls of various
    animals to protect their identities from one another. These masks are our mark. Symbols of death
    and decay. We must unmask the cultists to expose and derail their plans. We have but a few hours.
    The more cultists we find before midnight, the better.\"</string>
    <string name="midnight_setup_b"><b>Scenario 2: The Midnight Masks</b>\n
        \nIn the wake of the disaster at your home, Lita Chantler, the
    red-haired woman from your parlor, lays out a tale that - even in light of what you have just
    witnessed - strains the limits of your belief. \"The creatures in your home,\" she claims,
    \"are called ghouls - cruel beings who plague the crypts, caverns, and tunnels beneat the city
    of Arkham&#8230;\"\n
    \n\"These creatures feed on the corpses of humans, and they are
    served by a dark cult within Arkham whose members have inexplicably come to worship the ancient
    master of the ghouls. This cult has been killing innocent people and feeding them to the ghouls,
    satiating a monstrous hunger. A dark balance was maintained. Until now. Recently,\" Lita continues,
    \"one of their lairs, where the corpses were stored, was destroyed. Since then, the ghouls have
    been more active than usual. I have tracked their movements and tried my best to stop them from
    running amok throughout the city. But I think there is something worse going on. The cult has been
    planning something darker, and more ominous, than anything I have yet observed. Indicates are
    that this plan shall come to fruition tonight, shortly after midnight. Beyond that, I cannot
    fathom what to expect.\n
    \n\"Many of the cultists,\" Lita continues, \"will seem like everyday people, despite their foul
    intentions. Whenever the cult meets, its members don masks shaped like the skulls of various
    animals to protect their identities from one another. These masks are our mark. Symbols of death
    and decay. We must unmask the cultists to expose and derail their plans. We have but a few hours.
    The more cultists we find before midnight, the better.\"</string>

    <string name="midnight_sets">The Midnight Masks, Chilling Cold, Nightgaunts, Dark Cult, and Locked Doors.</string>
    <string name="midnight_set_aside">Cult of Umordhoth encounter set as a separate \"Cultist
        Deck\".\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_locations">Choose one of the two Downtown locations and one of the two Southside
        locations at random and put them into play. Remove the other versions of Downtown and Southside from
        the game.\n
        \nPut the Northside, Easttown, Rivertown, St. Mary\'s Hospital, Graveyard, Miskatonic
        University, and Your House locations into play.\n
    \nEvery investigator begins play at Your House.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_locations_no_house">Choose one of the two Downtown locations and one of the two Southside
        locations at random and put them into play. Remove the other versions of Downtown and Southside from
        the game.\n
        \nPut the Northside, Easttown, Rivertown, St. Mary\'s Hospital, Graveyard, and Miskatonic
        University locations into play.\n
        \nRemove Your House from the game.\n
    \nEvery investigator begins play at Rivertown.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_two">Search the gathered encounter sets for 1 copy of Acolyte and spawn
        it at Southside.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_three">Search the gathered encounter sets for 2 copies of Acolyte. Spawn
        1 at Southside and 1 at Downtown.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_four">Search the gathered encounter sets for 3 copies of Acolyte. Spawn
        1 at Southside,  1 at Downtown, and 1 at the Graveyard.\n</string>

    <string name="midnight_resolution_one">You\'ve managed to obtain some useful information about
    the cult and its plans. You can only hope it\'s enough.</string>
    <string name="midnight_resolution_two">Twelve bells ring out, signaling midnight. You\'re out
    of time; the cult\'s ritual will begin shortly. You\'ve managed to obtain some useful information
    about the cult and its plans. You can only hope it\'s enough.</string>

    <!--Scenario Three - The Devourer Below-->

    <string name="devourer_setup"><b>Scenario 3: The Devourer Below</b>\n
        \nAfter a frantic nighttime search throughout Arkham, you have tracked
    down and questioned several members of the cult. Your finds are disturbing: they claim to worship
    a being known as Umordhoth, a monstrous entity from another realm.\n
    \nYou are able to confirm much of Lita\'s story: the cult is agitated over the destruction of a
    ghoul lair. However, a surprising detail also turns up: the one who invaded the lair and set this
    night\'s events in motion was none other than Lita Chantler herself! You are not sure why this
    important detail was omitted from Lita\'s story - did she tell you only as much as was necessary
    to draw you into her conflict? But in another light, she seems to be fighting to protect the city
    of Arkham from a terrible menace.\n
    \nThe final piece of the puzzle was found written in a journal possessed by one of the cultists.
    It describes a dark ritual to be performed deep within the woods south of Arkham, this very night.
    According to the journal, the ritual\'s completion will open a gate and bring forth the cult\'s
    dark master into this world. \"If the cult is not stopped,\" Lita warns, \"there is a possibility
    that Umordhoth\'s vengeance will consume all in its path.\" Frightened but determined to stop
    the ritual, you head into the woods&#8230;</string>

    <string name="devourer_sets">The Devourer Below, Ancient Evils, Striking Fear, Ghouls, and Dark
        Cult.</string>
    <string name="devourer_sets_two">Randomly choose one of the following 4 encounter sets:\n
    \nAgents of Yog-Sothoth, Agents of Shub-Niggurath, Agents of Cthulhu, or Agents of Hastur.</string>
    <string name="devourer_set_aside">The Ritual Site and Umordhoth cards.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_locations">Put the Main Path location into play. Shuffle the 6 copies of Arkham
        Woods, choose 4 of them at random, and put them into play without looking at their revealed sides.
        Remove the other 2 from the game.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Main Path.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_additional">Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_additional_midnight">Each player discards 2 random cards from his or her starting
        hand.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_one">Place 1 doom on Agenda 1a.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_two">Place 2 doom on Agenda 1a.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_three">Place 3 doom on Agenda 1a.\n</string>

    <string name="umordhoth_succumbed">Arkham succumbed to Umordhoth\'s terrible vengeance.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_broken">The ritual to summon Umordhoth was broken.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_repelled">The investigators repelled Umordhoth.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_sacrificed">The investigators sacrificed Lita Chantler to Umordhoth.
    \nRandom <i>Madness</i> weakness added to each investigator\'s deck.\n</string>

    <string name="devourer_no_resolution">Too frightened to face her fate, Lita flees into the night.
    She realizes that she has failed and Umordhoth\'s vengeance will pursue her wherever she goes.
    The creature\'s tendrils spread throughout the city of Arkham, searching for her. It lurks in the
    darkness of every corner, tugging at the seams of reality. But Lita is nowhere to be found, so the
    creature dwells in the shadows to this day, searching&#8230;killing.\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose.</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_one">You have managed to prevent the cult from summoning its
    master. Although you\'re unsure what would have happened had the cult succeeded, you\'re relieved
    that - at least for the time being - Arkham is safe. You capture as many cultists as you can find,
    but very few townspeople believe your tale. Perhaps it was all in your head, after all.\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_two">Through force of arms and strength of will, you are
    somehow able to harm Umordhoth enough to send it reeling back to the dimension from which it
    emerged. Warmth and light return to the woods as the void-like mass is sucked in upon itself,
    vanishing in an instant. You aren\'t sure if a being such as this can be killed, but for the time
    being it seems to have retreated. As their master vanishes, the ghouls nearby climb into the open
    pit below, fleeing with terrible cries and shrieks. You have stopped an evil plot, but the fight
    has taken its toll on your body and mind. Worse, you can\'t help but feel insignificant in the
    face of the world\'s mysteries. What other terrors exist in the deep, dark corners of reality?\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_three">In the face of this horror, you don\'t believe there is
    anything you can do to stop it. You have but one hope if you are to survive. You turn on Lita and
    throw her at the terrible monstrosity, watching in dread as its swirling void-like mass consumes
    her. She cries out in torment as the life is sucked from her body. \"Umordhoth&#8230;Umordhoth&#8230;\"
    the cultists chant. Lita Chantler vanishes without a trace. For a moment, you fear that the creature
    will turn on you, but you hear one of the cultists say, \"Umordhoth is a just god who claims only
    the guilty and the dead. Go, and you shall be spared.\" The swirling mass vanishes, and warmth
    and light return to the woods. The cultists slink away, leaving you alive. Lita\'s last moments
    are forever etched upon your memory.\n
        \n<b>The guilt over sacrificing Lita forever haunts your memory. Each investigator must search the
            collection for a random <i>Madness</i> weakness and add it to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>The investigators have survived, but their actions weigh heavily on their consciences.</b></string>


    <!--The Dunwich Legacy-->

    <string name="dunwich_campaign_name">The Dunwich Legacy</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_one">Scenario 1-A: Extracurricular Activity</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_two">Scenario 1-B: The House Always Wins</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_three">Scenario 2: The Miskatonic Museum</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_four">Scenario 3: The Essex County Express</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_five">Blood on the Altar</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_six">Undimensional and Unseen</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_seven">Where Doom Awaits</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_eight">Lost in Time and Space</string>
    <string name="dunwich_interlude_one">Interlude 1: Armitage\'s Fate</string>

    <!--Miscellaneous-->
    <string name="cheated_checkbox">An investigator \"cheated\"</string>
    <string name="cheated_text">Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.\n</string>

    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="investigators_unconscious">The investigators were unconscious for several hours.\n</string>
    <string name="warren_kidnapped">Professor Warren Rice was kidnapped.\n</string>
    <string name="warren_rescued">The investigators rescued Professor Warren Rice.\n</string>
    <string name="students_failed">The investigators failed to save the students.\nTablet chaos token added to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.\n</string>
    <string name="students_rescued">The students were rescued.\n</string>
    <string name="experiment_defeated">The Experiment was defeated.\n</string>
    <string name="obannion_failed">The O\'Bannion gang has a bone to pick with the investigators.\n</string>
    <string name="obannion_succeeded">Naomi has the investigators\' backs.\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_kidnapped">Dr. Francis Morgan was kidnapped.\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_rescued">The investigators rescued Dr. Francis Morgan.\n</string>
    <string name="cheated">Elder Thing chaos token added to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_kidnapped">Dr. Herny Armitage was kidnapped.\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_rescued">The investigators rescued Dr. Henry Armitage.\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_failed">The investigators failed to recover the <i>Necronomicon</i>.\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_destroyed">The investigators destroyed the <i>Necronomicon</i>.\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_taken">The investigators took custody of the <i>Necronomicon</i>.
        \nThe Necronomicon (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>) added to an investigator\'s deck.
        \nElder Thing chaos token added to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.\n</string>

    <string name="dunwich_setup"><b>Prologue</b>\n
    \nDr. Henry Armitage pours himself a glass of pinot and sits down at his desk, gesturing for you to sit
        across from him. \"I apologize for the short notice,\" he begins. His face is pale, his forehead sweaty
        and wrinkled with worry.\n
    \nArmitage - the head librarian of Miskatonic University, and a former mentor of yours - privately
        contacted you in the hopes of gaining your assistance. Eager to help, you made your way to his home in
        Southside. Upon entering, you were surprised to find his home in disarray. Books and notes litter his
        desk, and an empty bottle of wine has tipped over onto the ground by the fireplace. You\'d always known
        Armitage to be neat and well-organized.\n
    \nThe elderly man takes a moment to collect his thoughts. \"I am looking for two of my colleagues - Dr.
        Francis Morgan, professor archaeology, and Warren Rice, professor of languages. Warren was supposed to
        meet up with me over supper earlier today to discuss several important findings, but he has since gone
        missing. At first I thought nothing of it, but I have a nagging feeling something else is going on. A
        very&#8230;<b>familiar</b> feeling.\" You\'ve never seen Armitage quite this worried before. His hands
        tremble as he reaches for the glass on his desk, and he sips from it nervously. \"I tried to find
        Francis, hoping he knew where Warren was, but he too is out of touch. Francis has been spending a lot
        of time in some gambling den, or so I am told.\n
    \n\"I sent for you because I am worried Warren might be in trouble. I would appreciate it greatly if you
        could find him for me. You may also wish to ask Francis for help, if you can reach him.\"</string>
    <string-array name="dunwich_setup_options">
        <item>Professor Warren Rice was last seen working late at night in the humanities department of
            Miskatonic University. Let\'s search for him there.\n</item>
        <item>Dr. Francis Morgan was last seen gambling at the Clover Club, an upscale speakeasy and gambling
            joint located downtown. Let\'s go talk to him.\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Scenario 1-A - Extracurricular Activity-->
    <string name="extracurricular_setup"><b>Scenario 1-A: Extracurricular Activity</b>\n
    \nDr. Armitage is worried his colleague, Professor Warren Rice, might be in trouble, so he has asked for
        your help in finding his friend. He seems unreasonably nervous about his colleague\'s disappearance,
        considering Professor Rice has only been \"missing\" for a matter of hours&#8230;</string>

    <string name="extracurricular_sets">Extracurricular Activity, Sorcery, The Beyond, Bishop\'s Thralls,
        Whippoorwills, Ancient Evils, Locked Doors, and Agents of Yog-Sothoth.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_set_aside_one">Faculty Offices (The Night is Still Young), \"Jazz\" Mulligan,
        Alchemical Concoction, The Experiment, Professor Warren Rice, Dormitories, and Alchemy Labs.\n</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_set_aside_two">Faculty Offices (The Hour is Late), \"Jazz\" Mulligan,
        Alchemical Concoction, The Experiment, Professor Warren Rice, Dormitories, and Alchemy Labs.\n</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_locations">Put the Miskatonic Quad, Orne Library, Humanities Building,
        Student Union, Science Building, and Administration Building locations into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Miskatonic Quad.\n</string>

    <string name="extracurricular_no_resolution">As you flee from the university, you hear screaming from the
        northern end of the campus. An ambulance passes you by, and you fear for the worst. Hours later, you
        learn that a \'rabid dog of some sort\' found its way into the university dormitories. The creature
        attacked the students inside and many were mauled or killed in the attack.\n
    \n<b>Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_one">You find Professor Rice bound and gagged in the closet of his
    office. When you free him, he informs you that the strange men and women wandering around the campus had
        been stalking him for hours. They cornered him in his office and tied him up, although for what
        purpose, Rice isn\'t sure. You inform him that Dr. Armitage sent you, and Rice looks relieved, although
    he suspects that Dr. Morgan might be in danger as well. Because the strangers on campus seem to have been
        targeting Professor Rice, you decide that the best course of action is to escort him away from the
        campus as quickly as possible. As you leave the university, you hear screaming from the northern end of
    the campus. An ambulance passes you by, and you fear for the worst. Hours later, you
        learn that a \'rabid dog of some sort\' found its way into the university dormitories. The creature
        attacked the students inside and many were mauled or killed in the attack.\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Professor Warren Rice to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_two">You pull each of the dormitory\'s fire alarms and usher the
        sutdents out of the building\'s north exit, hoping to make your way off campus. Many of the students
        are confused and exhausted, but you believe an attempt to explain the situation will do more harm than
        good. Minutes later, a terrible screech echoes across the campus, piercing and shrill. You tell the
        students to wait and head back to the dormitories to investigate. Oddly, you find no trace of the
        strange creature - a prospect that worries you more than it relieves you. You hurry to the faculty
        offices to find Professor Rice, but there is no sign of him anywhere.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_three">After defeating the strange and terrifying creature from
        the Department of Alchemy, you rush to the faculty offices to find Professor Rice. By the time you to
        his office, there is no sign of him anywhere.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_four">You awaken hours later, exhausted and injured. You\'re not
        sure what you saw, but the sight of it filled your mind with terror. From other survivors, you learn
        that a \'rabid dog of some sort\' found its way into the university dormitories. The creature
        attacked the students inside and many were mauled or killed in the attack.\n
    \n<b>Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.</b></string>


    <!--Scenario 1-B - The House Always Wins-->
    <string name="house_setup"><b>Scenario 1-B: The House Always Wins</b>\n
    \nDr. Armitage suggested you track down his associate Dr. Francis Morgan. He\'s not sure whether Dr. Morgan
    is in trouble, but he\'s not particularly happy with his colleague\'s present choice of company. He\'s in
        the Clover Club, a notorious gambling joint somewhere downtown. Finding the club\'s exact location
        isn\'t easy - you have to grease a few palms just to learn which of the Downtown restaurants operates
        as the club\'s front. That restaurant is La Bella Luna, a somewhat upscale Italian eatery by the
        theatre. You change into your Sunday best and make your way there.\n
    \nIn front of La Bella Luna stands a man in a pinstripe suit who sizes you up as you approach. \"Enjoy
        yourselves,\" he says with a snake-like grin as he holds open the restaurant\'s front door.</string>

    <string name="house_sets">The House Always Wins, Bad Luck, Naomi\'s Crew, and Rats.</string>
    <string name="house_set_aside">The Hideous Abominations and Striking Fear encounter sets.\n</string>
    <string name="house_set_aside_two">Darkened Hall, Peter Clover, Dr. Francis Morgan, and each copy of Back
        Hall Doorway.\n</string>
    <string name="house_locations">Put the Clover Club Lounge, Clover Club Bar, Clover Club Cardroom, and La
        Bella Luna locations into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play in La Bella Luna.\n</string>
    <string name="house_additional">Put Clover Club Pit Boss into play in the Clover Club Lounge.\n</string>

    <string name="house_resolution_one">You flee to the end of the block and pause to recover. Before you can
        catch your breath, the ground shakes with a thunderous crash. People emerge from their homes and
        storefronts to see what the ruckus is, and a crowd forms on the street. You head to the front of the
        crowd and are horrified to see the building from which you fled just minutes earlier reduced to rubble.
        There is no sign of Dr. Morgan anywhere.</string>
    <string name="house_resolution_two">\"What in the world&#8230;?\" Dr. Morgan finally breaks out of his daze
        as you make your way to safety. You ask him what he remembers, and he sputters and shakes his head.
        \"It\'s all a haze,\" he explains, visibly exhausted. \"I was having the run of my life! Perhaps I had
        one too many shots. But, those creatures - I haven\'t seen anything like that since&#8230;\" He trails
        off, and you can tell that his mind is racing. His eyes widen with realization and his face pales. \"I
        may not be in the best shape, but I\'ll help with your investigation. Whatever it takes.\"\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Dr. Francis Morgan to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="house_resolution_three">Although you were unable to find Dr. Morgan in the club, the man you
        rescued is grateful for your help. He introduces himself as Peter Clover, the owner of the
        establishment you\'d just left. Despite the situatin, he maintains an air of quiet professionalism. As
        you make your way towards the street, a well-polished Chrysler B-70 rolls up to you, and a gorgeous
        woman with long brown hair and narrow eyes exits. She is flanked by dangerous-looking men who slip
        their hands under their suit jackets when they see you. \"Peter,\" she says with a sigh of relief,
        \"Good, you\'re okay. I heard there was trouble?\" She turns and glares at you with deadly eyes. \"Who
        are they?\"\n
    \nMr. Clover dusts off his vest, unworried. \"Naomi, my dear, these are friends of mine. They&#8230;\" he
        clears his throat. \"They escorted me off the premises,\" he explains after a short pause. \"They have
        earned our gratitude.\" The woman crosses her arms and takes a moment to size you up before giving you
        a smirk.\n
    \n\"Very well then. I must thank you for taking care of Peter. Run along now; we\'ll handle things from
        here.\" She nods to the goons flanking her and they walk past you toward the club\'s rear entrance,
        pulling firearms out from underneath their coats. You\'re not sure what \'handling things\' means, but
        you\'re pretty sure you don\'t want to be here when the gunfire starts. You thank Naomi and Peter, and
        head off.</string>
    <string name="house_resolution_four">You are pulled from the debris by several firefighters, on of whom
        exclaims, \"We\'ve got a live one!\" A few of them patch you up, and the cops ask you what happened.
        You\'re certain they wouldn\'t believe your story about horrible monstrosities demolishing the building
    from within. Unsure of what to say, you give a vague statement about not remembering much. \"We\'re
        bringing you to St. Mary\'s,\" one of the nurses says, pointing to a nearby ambulance. Knowing now how
        dire the situation is, you slip away while she is distracted by something else in the rubble&#8230;</string>


    <!--Interlude 1: Armitage's Fate-->
    <string name="dunwich_interlude_one_text"><b>Armitage\'s Fate</b>\n
    \nYou are more than a little rattled by your experiences in the university and the Clover Club. You\'re not
        sure what to make of whoever - or whatever - was after Rice and Morgan. Worried about Dr. Armitage, you
        swiftly make your way back to his home. When you arrive, you find that the latches of his front door
        have been busted open, and his living area and study have been ransacked. Dr. Armitage is nowhere to be
        found. Searching his home, you find a journal the intruders didn\'t steal tucked beneath several other
        documents in the bottom drawer of Armitage\'s desk. The journal appears to be written in a strange
        language you cannot decode, using a script you\'ve never seen in your entire life. Fortunately, it
        seems Dr. Armitage had already gone through the trouble of translating it into English. Apparently, it
        belongs to one \"Wilbur Whateley.\"\n
    \nThe journal - along with Armitage\'s many notes - tells a startling tale, one you would scarcely believe
        had it not been for your harrowing experiences earlier tonight&#8230;</string>
    <string name="dunwich_interlude_two_text"><b>Armitage\'s Fate</b>\n
    \nWhen you arrive at Dr. Armitage\'s home in Southside, you find him sitting at his desk, pale-faced and
        sweating with worry. He is grateful to you for searching for his colleagues, but he doesn\'t look
        relieved. With a long pause, he straightens his glasses and explains:\n
    \n\"I\'m afraid I must apologize. There\'s something I didn\'t mention to you earlier.\" Dr. Armitage then
        spins a tale that you would scarcely believe had it not been for your harrowing experiences earlier
        that night&#8230;\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Dr. Henry Armitage to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <!--Scenario 2: The Miskatonic Museum-->
    <string name="miskatonic_setup_a"><b>Scenario 2: The Miskatonic Museum</b>\n
    \nSeveral months ago, Armitage and his colleagues stopped a rampaging horror from tearing through Dunwich,
        a backwater town several hours north and west of Arkham. At first you imagine this beast as a rabid
        bear, or worse, but the professor\'s description of the creature paints a different picture.\n
    \nIt all began when a man named Wilbur Whately entered the Orne Library looking for Olaus Wormius\'s Latin
        translation of a book called the <i>Necronomicon</i>. Wilbur already possessed a beaten-up English
        translation by Dr. John Dee, but it was insufficient for his purposes. Armitage turned the man away,
        fearing what use the strange man had for the book. Whateley returned in secret, hoping to steal the
        book, but was attacked by a hound guarding the university. Armitage, Rice, and Morgan later discovered
        Whateley\'s body. A description of the foul corpse - semi-anthropomorphic and covered in fur, with a
        leathery hide and greenish-grey tentacles - causes you to question whether or not Whateley was truly
        human.\n
        \nThe notes written by Dr. Armitage in the journal stress Whateley\'s
        desire to get his hands on the <i>Necronomicon</i> for some terrible purpose. As you read on, it seems
        that Dr. Armitage brought the university\'s copy of the tome to Harold Walsted - the curator of the
        Miskatonic Museum - for safekeeping in the museum\'s Restricted Hall. Although you are worried about
        your mentor, you are equally worried that Armitage\'s kidnappers might get their hands on the
        <i>Necronomicon</i>. You decide to head to the museum to prevent them from acquiring it.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_setup_b"><b>Scenario 2: The Miskatonic Museum</b>\n
    \nSeveral months ago, Armitage and his colleagues stopped a rampaging horror from tearing through Dunwich,
        a backwater town several hours north and west of Arkham. At first you imagine this beast as a rabid
        bear, or worse, but the professor\'s description of the creature paints a different picture.\n
    \nIt all began when a man named Wilbur Whately entered the Orne Library looking for Olaus Wormius\'s Latin
        translation of a book called the <i>Necronomicon</i>. Wilbur already possessed a beaten-up English
        translation by Dr. John Dee, but it was insufficient for his purposes. Armitage turned the man away,
        fearing what use the strange man had for the book. Whateley returned in secret, hoping to steal the
        book, but was attacked by a hound guarding the university. Armitage, Rice, and Morgan later discovered
        Whateley\'s body. A description of the foul corpse - semi-anthropomorphic and covered in fur, with a
        leathery hide and greenish-grey tentacles - causes you to question whether or not Whateley was truly
        human.\n
        \n\"My colleagues and I were quick to put the ordeal behind us,\"
        Armitage says with a sigh. \"But it seems that things haven\'t fully resolved themselves. I\'ll tell
        you the rest later, but for now, it is imperative that we get our hands on that copy of the
        <i>Necronomicon</i>. If my instincts are correct, the assailants you\'ve encountered will be searching
        for it. After all that transpired, I didn\'t feel safe keeping at the library, so I brought it to my
        good friend, Harold Walsted. He is the current curator of the Miskatonic Museum. I thought it would be
        safe in the museum\'s Restricted Hall, but now I\'m not so sure. You must retrieve it at all costs! I
        fear terribly what they could do with the rites contianed in its pages&#8230;\"</string>

    <string name="miskatonic_sets">The Miskatonic Museum, Bad Luck, Sorcery, The Beyond, Chilling Cold, and
        Locked Doors.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_locations">Put one of the two Administration Office locations and one of the two
        Security Office locations into play at random. Remove the other versions from the game. Then, put the
        Museum Entrance and Museum Halls locations into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at the Museum Entrance.\n</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_set_aside">Harold Walsted, Adam Lynch, The Necronomicon
        (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>), and Shadow-spawned.\n</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_additional">Set the 6 "Exhibit Hall" locations aside as a separate "Exhibit Deck."
        To do this, perform the following:\n
    \nShuffle the Exhibit Hall (<i>Restricted Hall</i>) and 2 other random Exhibit Hall locations together to
        form the bottom 3 cards of the Exhibit Deck, unrevealed side faceup.\n
    \nThen, place the other 3 Exhibit Hall locations on top, in a random order. All 6 cards of the Exhibit Hall
    deck should be showing only the unrevealed side, so that the players do not know which Exhibit Hall is the
        Exhibit Hall (<i>Restricted Hall</i>).\n</string>

    <string name="miskatonic_no_resolution">Whatever the creature in the museum was, you had neither the will
        nor the tools to destroy it. It seems you must give up any hope of recovering the <i>Necronomicon</i>.
        Even so, there are others depending on you. Gathering your courage, you prepare for your next task.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_resolution_one">As long as this translation of the <i>Necronomicon</i> exists,
        there will be sorcerers and other foul agents like Whateley seeking it. In the end, you know what must
        be done to protect humanity from the threats you\'ve seen. You find a trash bin and fill it with books
        and documents, throwing the <i>Necronomicon</i> on top. It takes several matches to set the contents of
    the bin alight. The flames fill the room with heat and the creeping shadows retreat from its light. You
        watch the book burn for some time, its pages turning to ash. You can only hope you\'ve made the right
        decision.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_resolution_two">The <i>Necronomicon</i> is more than just a book; it is a tool.
        Within its pages is a wealth of information about the forces and creatures you have encountered.
        Knowing how useful it could be in your endeavors, how could you possibly bring yourself to destroy it?
        Besides, as long as you keep the book safely in your possession, you will still be foiling those who
        wish to use it for nefarious purposes.\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add The Necronomicon (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>) to his or her
     deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>You have given in to the temptation of power. Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the
            remainder of the campaign.</b></string>


    <!--Side stories-->
    <string-array name="side_stories">
        <item>Curse of the Rougarou</item>
        <item>Carnevale of Horrors</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Curse of the Rougarou-->
    <string name="rougarou_setup"><b>Curse of the Rougarou</b>\n
        \n<b>Terror Grips New Orleans!</b>\n
    \nMinnie Klein, your contact at the Arkham Advertiser, had slipped you a draft of the article over a cup of
        coffee at Velma\'s Diner. It would have gone to print had Doyle Jeffries, the lead editor, not scoffed at
        the concept. \"I believe his exact words were, \'I ain\'t printing the ravings of some Voodoo lunatic
        and passing it off as news,\'\" she explained. From the sly grin spreading across her face, you could
        tell she smelled a story.\n
    \nThe headline was sensationalist. Three killings in nine days was enough to spook a town, sure. But you
        doubt all of New Orleans is gripped by terror, or even knows about the killings. Still, something
        piqued your interest. \"Lady Esprit,\" the Voodoo priestess from the article, claimed that a malign
        curse had taken root in the bayou.\n
    \n\"There\'s something to this, isn\'t there? I know that look,\" Minnie said. You weren\'t sure. If Lady
        Esprit was right, this \"roux-ga-roux\" wouldn\'t stop killing at three, that\'s for sure. But curses?
        Wolf-people? How could such things be real? Only one way to find out. You put on your coat and head for
        the Northside station&#8230;</string>
    <string name="rougarou_sets">The Bayou.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_locations">Sort each of the locations into 4 piles, by trait (New Orleans,
        Riverside, Wilderness, and Unhallowed). Randomly choose 1 of these piles and remove those locations
        from the game. Randomly choose another 1 of these piles and put those locations into play.\n
        Each investigator begins play at a Bayou location in play.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside">Curse of the Rougarou encounter set.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside_two">Each location in the other 2 piles, Lady Esprit, Bear Trap, and Fishing Net.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_one">Somehow, you manage to make it back to safety before daybreak,
        resting until late afternoon. It isn\'t until you seek out Lady Esprit the next day that you realize
        who last night\'s victim was. With a heavy heart and an unshakeable dread, you choose to bury her body
        instead of contacting the authorities - the less people who delve this deep into the bayou, the better.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_two">The creature gives a pitiful wail as dark miry blood oozes from its
        wounds. By the time its body collapses into the mud, it has transformed back into its original form -
        the form of a young dark-skinned man, his expression twisted in agony. You bring his body back to Lady
        Esprit and she works her strange magic, removing the stain of the curse from the land. \"Call on me
        should you ever need my help,\" the mysterious woman tells you.\n
        \n<b>Remove the Curse of the Rougarou weakness from it\'s bearer\'s deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Lady Esprit to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_three">Somehow, you have managed to quell the rage and bloodlust of the
        curse within the creature, and in moments the shape of a young, dark-skinned man stands before you,
        panting and sweating. He seems to only just now understand everything he\'s done, and agrees to flee to
    a secluded corner of the earth where he can harm no one. However, the curse lives on. He sees it in your
        eyes and grips your arm tightly. \"Don\'t let it take control,\" he warns. \"I was weak, but you - I
        can tell you are strong. Control the curse as I could not.\"\n
    \n<b>The bearer of the Curse of the Rougarou weakness must add Monstrous Transformation to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="rougarou_alive">The Rougarou continues to haunt the bayou.\nCurse of the Rougarou weakness added to
        an investigator\'s deck.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_destroyed">The Rougarou is destroyed, and the curse is lifted.\nLady Esprit added to an investigator\'s deck.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_escaped">The Rougarou escaped, and you embraced the curse.\nCurse of the Rougarou weakness
        and Monstrous Transformation added to an investigator\'s deck.\n</string>

    <!--Carnevale of Horrors-->
    <string name="carnevale_setup"><b>Carnevale of Horrors</b>\n
        \n<b>The Carnevale is Coming&#8230;</b>\n
    \n\"Look,\" Sheriff Engel insists, \"I know it sounds crazy, but that\'s all there is to it.\" He sighs and
    sits back down, pouring a cup of joe for you and one for himself. \"A dame in Uptown spotted a cracked egg
        wearing this mask and holdin\' a bloody butcher\'s cleaver,\" he says, motioning to the black leather
        mask sitting on his desk. It has a comically long nose and a strange symbol scrawled in yellow on its
        forehead. \"So, she calls it in. My boys and I picked him up on the corner of Saltonstall &amp;
        Garrison.\" The sheriff\'s jaw clenches and his brows furrow as he recounts the story. \"Fella did
        nothing but laugh as we slapped the bracelets on him. Called himself Zanni. Said nothing except the
        \'carnival is coming,\' whatever the hell that meant. Wasn\'t until the next day we found the victim\'s
    body. Defense wanted him in a straitjacket. We were happy to oblige.\"\n
    \nThere isn\'t much time to spare. If your research is right, there is more to this case than meets the eye
        . This \"Zanni\" wasn\'t talking about Darke\'s Carnival, but rather, the Carnevale of Venice, which
        begins just before the next full moon&#8230;</string>
    <string name="carnevale_sets">Carnevale of Horrors</string>
    <string name="carnevale_locations">Choose 1 location at random and remove it from the game. If San Marco
        Basilica or Canal-side is chosen, randomly choose a different location instead.\n
        Put the other 8 locations into play, in a random circular formation.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at San Marco Basilica.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_set_aside">Cnidathqua, Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, and Gilded Volto.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_additional">Put Abbess Allegria Di Biase into play at San Marco Basilica.\n
    \nShuffle the 7 Masked Carnevale-Goers and put 1 into play at each location other than San Marco Basilica,
        Masked Carnevale-Goer side face-up. Do not look at their other sides.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_no_resolution">You sputter awake as an oar gently taps your shoulder.
        \"<i>Tutto bene</i>?\" The gondolier holding the oar says with a concerned expression. You nod and drag
    yourself onto the docks from his gondola, drenched and aching all over. The city is devastated. Most of the
    boats in the canal are wrecked, and the streets are covered not in confetti, but in blood&#8230;\n
    \n<b>Move 1 Innocent Reveler from underneath the act deck to underneath the agenda deck, if able.</b>\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_one">The city is still recovering from the events during the eclipse.
        With nearly all evidence of the creature melted away by the hot sun, many attribute the violence during
    the Carnevale to local crime lord Cascio Di Boerio and his crew. Those that know the truth know better than
    the speak of the elder creature that lives in Laguna Veneta. With any luck, its name will never be spoken
        again.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_two">The creature recoils as globules of its jelly-like flesh rip and
        tear from its body, splashing into the lagoon. It makes no sound as its torn body sinks into the depths
        . The chanting in the city plunges into mournful silence. As you return it to the canal-side streets,
        black feathers fall from the sky where bright confetti once fluttered. You can only wonder how long it
        will take for the creature to recover.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_sacrifice">Too many lives were lost during the eclipse to stop the
        machinations of Cindathqua\'s servants. The beast has been fed, its minions empowered. You find
        yourself hoping you don\'t live long enough to see the fallout of your failure.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator searches the collection for a random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or
            <i>Monster</i> weakness and adds it to his or her deck for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_abbess">"<i>Grazie mille</i> - thank you for all your help,\" Allegria says
        as you return to the basilica. \"Thanks to you, there were few casualties. I shudder to think what
        might have happened had you not arrived. Should you ever require assistance, please do not hesitate to
        ask.\"\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Abbess Allegria Di Biase to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_many_sacrificed">Many were sacrificed to Cnidathqua during the Carnevale.\n<i>Mask</i> card added to each investigator\'s deck.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_banished">The sun banished Cnidathqua into the depths.\n<i>Mask</i> card added to each investigator\'s deck.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_retreated">Cnidathqua retreated to nurse its wounds.\n<i>Mask</i> card added to each investigator\'s deck.\n</string>
    <string-array name="carnevale_rewards">
        <item>No additional rewards</item>
        <item>Sacrifice Made</item>
        <item>Abbess Satisfied</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="carnevale_no_rewards">No additional rewards.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_sacrifice_made">Random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or <i>Monster</i> weakness
        added to each investigator\'s deck.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_abbess_satisfied">Abbess Allegria Di Biase added to an investigator\'s deck.</string>


</resources>
